{
    "subject": "resource/Kip_Moore",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Tifton,_Georgia",
    "human_readable": "Kip Moore was born in Tifton, Georgia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8845428228378296,
            "question": "Name the city where Kip Moore was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8819836974143982,
            "question": "Where was Kip Moore born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8678840398788452,
            "question": "In which state was Kip Moore born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45627835392951965,
            "question": "What is Kip Moore known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4314858913421631,
            "question": "Is Kip Moore a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42352184653282166,
            "question": "Where does Kip Moore currently reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23647238314151764,
            "question": "Who are some of Kip Moore's musical influences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22987698018550873,
            "question": "Has Kip Moore won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14324580132961273,
            "question": "What is Kip Moore's most popular song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13055774569511414,
            "question": "What genre of music does Kip Moore perform?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kip Moore was born in Tifton, Georgia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3493_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Kip Moore's most popular song?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3493_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Kip Moore won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3493_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of Kip Moore's musical influences?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3493_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3493_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3493_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3493_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3493_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3493_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3493_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3493_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3493_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3493_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3493_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After reviewing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"yes\" }`\n\nThe documents consistently mention that Kip Moore was indeed born in Tifton, Georgia. This birthplace is mentioned in multiple files and sources (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3493/re-ranker-msmarco/48.txt, 45.txt, 29.txt, 50.txt, and 22.txt), confirming the accuracy of this information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently state that Kip Moore was born in Tifton, Georgia. Therefore, the statement \"Kip Moore was born in Tifton, Georgia\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}